<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Aggregator News</title>
    <link>http://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android</link>
    <description>Latest news about Aggregator</description>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6540a28d-ad73-4f57-902b-a367f103c4f5</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.12.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h3>The <em>update history</em> is back!</h3>
<p>When I started to work on the new design of the update history I had these goals:</p>
<ul>
<li>make it scrollable to cover a longer period of time</li>
<li>include visual hints for the passed time between updates</li>
<li>provide extended details for each update</li>
</ul>
<p>To access the <em>update history</em>, navigate to a feed and select the <code>Update history</code>
option from the overflow menu. If Aggregator failed to update the feed, the <code>Update
history</code> option is available directly in the action bar.</p>
<p><img alt="update history" src="images/00008/device-2016-07-06-204317.png" /></p>
<p><img alt="update details" src="images/00008/device-2016-07-06-213455.png" /></p>
<p>Also, in the navigation drawer, feeds that failed to be updated are now highlighted.</p>
<p><img alt="highlighted feeds" src="images/00008/device-2016-07-06-203852.png" /></p>
<h3>Redirects</h3>
<p>Starting with this version, Aggregator will handle both temporary and permanent redirects.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 08:58:00 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b357595-c98a-419d-ac50-dfd61eb6c188</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.11.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>You can directly open the original article with the browser by pressing entry's feed icon in the entries list.</li>
<li>Long pressing the entry's feed icon, navigates you to that feed.</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 10:41:00 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f550a9e-053b-4ed9-90a1-d50f81000d2c</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.10.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Renamed the <strong>Unread</strong> category to <strong>All</strong>, and added the option to show the read entries</li>
<li>The <strong>Show read entries</strong> is now permanent</li>
<li>Increased the entry list font size</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 14:45:00 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">376d0a34-b377-428e-8967-6ddcaa0d2500</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.9.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Pull to refresh! Works on every entry list (unread, category or feed)</li>
<li>The update scheduler groups now feeds in slots of 15 minutes, for better battery life</li>
<li>D-Pad navigation support</li>
<li>Fixed the global entry rules</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 11:19:32 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d306ca28-a2e3-425c-a112-9b9d1b945940</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.8.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Full support for the Android 6.0 permission model</li>
<li>The exported OPML file includes now the entry rules too</li>
<li>Support for media description (present in feeds from Youtube)</li>
<li>The feed category is now displayed for each feed entry</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 12:27:38 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73ebb000-74d5-11e5-8bcf-feff819cdc9f</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.7.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Aggregator 2.7.0 brings support for user-defined feed categories.</p>
<p><img alt="Screenshot" src="news/00003/device-2015-10-17-153825.png" /></p>
<p>Collapsing or expanding a category can be done by long-pressing it.</p>
<p>To a assign a feed to a category one has to go to the feed preference activity, also accessible via a long-press.</p>
<p>Other changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>light and dark themes for the entire app</li>
<li>fix for duplicate entries</li>
<li>fix for repeated notification sound and vibrations</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 14:30:00 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">addc60ac-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator Howto » Entry Rules</title>
      
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><strong>Aggregator</strong> uses user-defined entry rules to filter out the entries of a feed.</p>
<p>There are two types of rules: <strong>exclude rules</strong>, used to mark which entries should be hidden while aggregating a feed,
and <strong>include rules</strong>, used to cancel the effect of some exclude rules.</p>
<p>Every entry rule defines a <strong>mask</strong> used to match the entries for which the rule <strong>action</strong> is applied. The <code>%</code>
character is used to match zero, one or multiple characters, and can be used multiple times in a <strong>mask</strong>.</p>
<p>For example, the <code>%aggregator%</code> title mask will match every entry that contains <code>aggregator</code> in the title. While the <code>%
Vol % Ch %</code> title mask will match every entry that contains both <code>Vol</code> and <code>Ch</code> (in the same order as present in the
mask) in the title.</p>
<h2>Excluding unwished entries</h2>
<p>The easiest way to define rules that hide entries of a feed is by using the <strong>exclude</strong> action:</p>
<ol>
<li>Select the entry which you want to exclude by <em>long pressing</em> it.</li>
<li>Click the <em>exclude</em> action from the action bar.</li>
</ol>
<p><em>NOTE: Depending on your device type, the <strong>exclude</strong> action can be found either as as an action icon or as an option in
the overflow menu.</em></p>
<p><em>HINT: Long pressing an icon in the action bar reveals the action name.</em></p>
<h2>Excluding all entries except the whished ones</h2>
<p>This is achieved by defining at least two rules:</p>
<ol>
<li>An <strong>exclude</strong> rule that hides every entry by using the following title mask: <code>%</code></li>
<li>One or more <strong>include</strong> rules that will cancel the effect of the <strong>exclude</strong> rule.</li>
</ol>
<p>These rules are preferably created from the <em>entry rules</em> activity, which can be opened by clicking the <strong>entry rules</strong>
option from the overflow menu.</p>
<p><em>NOTE: The <strong>entry rules</strong> activity lists all the rules of a feed, including the global ones, while also showing how
many entries are matched by a rule.</em></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b9222c-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.6.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Aggregator is not dead... development is just (very) slow.</p>
<p>So what's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>redesigned UI</li>
<li>exclude and include rules for feed entries</li>
<li>entry reader with new "show original" option</li>
<li>feed:// support</li>
<li>pinned entries: which are shown are unread until manually marked as read</li>
</ul>
<p><img alt="Screenshot" src="news/00001/device-2015-04-11-141333.png" /></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 20:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>