<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Aggregator News</title>
    <link>https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android</link>
    <description>Latest news about Aggregator</description>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec447774-52db-4e37-b9ed-ca5e5c72719f</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.17.000</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Swipe to refresh works now at both the top and the bottom of the list. The same action now hides the read entries too.</p>
<p>The title of pinned entries has a more prominent color to be noticed more easily.</p>
<p>All layouts have been updated to support RTL languages... and I prepared a website for the ones interested in translating the app in their language. Drop me an e-mail if you want to help...</p>
<p><img alt="refresh action" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00013/device-2017-03-31-095617.gif" /></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a43468fa-0dd9-4b8f-9194-94bee81d2e79</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.16.000</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h3>More material design</h3>
<p>The <strong>mark all as read</strong> action has been converted to a <em>floating action button</em>, and its place has been taken by the <strong>refresh</strong> action.</p>
<p>To give a better idea what happens in the background, the refresh action shows now how many feeds are beeing syncronized... </p>
<p>Clicking the refresh action, while spinning, will display more details.</p>
<p><img alt="refresh action" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00013/device-2017-03-22-233451.gif" /></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 22:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8313549e-cf87-4222-a974-7e8e2c894a48</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.15.000</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h3>Entry list</h3>
<p>The entry list has received a facelift that dims down the noise produced by high-contrasted colors and allows the reader to focus more on the content.</p>
<p><img alt="entry list" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00012/device-2017-03-22-220123.png" /></p>
<p>Unread entries now appear in bold while read entries are grayed out.
Feeds annotated with a color have a colored bullet in front of the entry time.</p>
<h3>OPML</h3>
<p>The feeds import and export activities display now the feed categories in a similar way to the entry list...</p>
<p><img alt="entry list" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00012/device-2017-03-22-220536.png" /></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c5233b8-6c60-445e-bfe2-cf9bb198ade2</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.14.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>In the past weeks I received a lot of emails with questions on how the entry rules work...</p>
<p>Even though this feed already provides an howto related to this topic, the majority of users doesn't use it (some users forgot about it while others lost access to it by unsubscribing from this feed).</p>
<p>Starting with this release, the same howto is now available right from the <em>create entry rule</em> activity...</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d8400d3-dee3-47ba-87e4-2c7f6e13be60</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.13.5</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Unfortunately, the <a href="https://developers.google.com/feed/">Google Feed API</a> service has been discontinued on 15 December 2016.</p>
<p>As a result, the <em>find feeds by keywords</em> feature has stopped functionning... and with this release I removed it entirely.</p>
<p>If you are aware of another free service that provides a similar functionality, drop me an email...</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 22:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50e525cd-9dd9-4eb3-bb69-c998125529ba</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.13.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Android 5+ only:</strong> Aggregator takes advantage of the new <em>JobScheduler API</em>, to become more battery friendly</li>
<li>The displayed time respects now the user's time settings</li>
<li>When available, the author of an entry is displayed in entry lists and the embedded viewer</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 22:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6540a28d-ad73-4f57-902b-a367f103c4f5</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.12.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h3>The <em>update history</em> is back!</h3>
<p>When I started working on the new design of the update history I had these goals:</p>
<ul>
<li>make it scrollable to cover a longer period of time</li>
<li>include visual hints for the time passed between updates</li>
<li>provide extended details for each update</li>
</ul>
<p>To access the <em>update history</em>, navigate to a feed and select the <code>Update history</code>
option from the overflow menu. If Aggregator failed to update the feed, the <code>Update
history</code> option is available directly in the action bar.</p>
<p><img alt="update history" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00008/device-2016-07-06-204317.png" /></p>
<p><img alt="update details" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00008/device-2016-07-06-213455.png" /></p>
<p>Also, in the navigation drawer, feeds that failed to be updated are now highlighted.</p>
<p><img alt="highlighted feeds" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00008/device-2016-07-06-203852.png" /></p>
<h3>Redirects</h3>
<p>Starting with this version, Aggregator will handle both temporary and permanent
redirects.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b357595-c98a-419d-ac50-dfd61eb6c188</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.11.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>You can directly open the original article with the browser by pressing entry's feed icon in the entries list.</li>
<li>Long pressing the entry's feed icon, navigates you to that feed.</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f550a9e-053b-4ed9-90a1-d50f81000d2c</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.10.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Renamed the <strong>Unread</strong> category to <strong>All</strong>, and added the option to show the read entries</li>
<li>The <strong>Show read entries</strong> is now permanent</li>
<li>Increased the entry list font size</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">376d0a34-b377-428e-8967-6ddcaa0d2500</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.9.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Pull to refresh! Works on every entry list (unread, category or feed)</li>
<li>The update scheduler groups now feeds in slots of 15 minutes, for better battery life</li>
<li>D-Pad navigation support</li>
<li>Fixed the global entry rules</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 11:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d306ca28-a2e3-425c-a112-9b9d1b945940</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.8.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>What's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>Full support for the Android 6.0 permission model</li>
<li>The exported OPML file includes now the entry rules too</li>
<li>Support for media description (present in feeds from Youtube)</li>
<li>The feed category is now displayed for each feed entry</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 12:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73ebb000-74d5-11e5-8bcf-feff819cdc9f</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.7.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Aggregator 2.7.0 brings support for user-defined feed categories.</p>
<p><img alt="Screenshot" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00003/device-2015-10-17-153825.png" /></p>
<p>Collapsing or expanding a category can be done by long-pressing it.</p>
<p>To a assign a feed to a category one has to go to the feed preference activity, also accessible via a long-press.</p>
<p>Other changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>light and dark themes for the entire app</li>
<li>fix for duplicate entries</li>
<li>fix for repeated notification sound and vibrations</li>
</ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">addc60ac-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator Howto » Entry Rules</title>
      
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p><strong>Aggregator</strong> uses user-defined entry rules to filter out the entries of a feed.</p>
<p>There are two types of rules: <strong>exclude rules</strong>, used to mark which entries should be hidden while aggregating a feed,
and <strong>include rules</strong>, used to cancel the effect of some exclude rules.</p>
<p>Every entry rule defines a <strong>mask</strong> used to match the entries for which the rule <strong>action</strong> is applied. The <code>%</code>
character is used to match zero, one or multiple characters, and can be used multiple times in a <strong>mask</strong>.</p>
<p>For example, the <code>%aggregator%</code> title mask will match every entry that contains <code>aggregator</code> in the title. While the <code>%
Vol % Ch %</code> title mask will match every entry that contains both <code>Vol</code> and <code>Ch</code> (in the same order as present in the
mask) in the title.</p>
<h2>Excluding unwished entries</h2>
<p>The easiest way to define rules that hide entries of a feed is by using the <strong>exclude</strong> action:</p>
<ol>
<li>Select the entry which you want to exclude by <em>long pressing</em> it.</li>
<li>Click the <em>exclude</em> action from the action bar.</li>
</ol>
<p><em>NOTE: Depending on your device type, the <strong>exclude</strong> action can be found either as as an action icon or as an option in
the overflow menu.</em></p>
<p><em>HINT: Long pressing an icon in the action bar reveals the action name.</em></p>
<h2>Excluding all entries except the whished ones</h2>
<p>This is achieved by defining at least two rules:</p>
<ol>
<li>An <strong>exclude</strong> rule that hides every entry by using the following title mask: <code>%</code></li>
<li>One or more <strong>include</strong> rules that will cancel the effect of the <strong>exclude</strong> rule.</li>
</ol>
<p>These rules are preferably created from the <em>entry rules</em> activity, which can be opened by clicking the <strong>entry rules</strong>
option from the overflow menu.</p>
<p><em>NOTE: The <strong>entry rules</strong> activity lists all the rules of a feed, including the global ones, while also showing how
many entries are matched by a rule.</em></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b9222c-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.6.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Aggregator is not dead... development is just (very) slow.</p>
<p>So what's new?</p>
<ul>
<li>redesigned UI</li>
<li>exclude and include rules for feed entries</li>
<li>entry reader with new "show original" option</li>
<li>feed:// support</li>
<li>pinned entries: which are shown are unread until manually marked as read</li>
</ul>
<p><img alt="Screenshot" src="https://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android/news/00001/device-2015-04-11-141333.png" /></p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>