<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Aggregator News</title>
    <link>http://tughi.github.io/aggregator-android</link>
    <description>Latest news about Aggregator</description>
    <item>
      <guid>c1b9222c-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator 2.6.0</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tughi.aggregator</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>Aggregator is not dead... development is just (very) slow.</p>
          <p>So what's new?</b>
          <ul>
            <li>redesigned UI</li>
            <li>exclude and include rules for feed entries</li>
            <li>entry reader with new "show original" option</li>
            <li>feed:// support</li>
            <li>pinned entries: which are shown are unread until manually marked as read</li>
          </ul>
          <img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BVPJ48zWJmY/VSkQfjIMwCI/AAAAAAAAJB0/8YW2qQmCaPg/w540-h900-no/Screenshot_2015-04-11-14-13-33.png" />
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>addc60ac-1daf-11e5-9a21-1697f925ec7b</guid>
      <title>Aggregator Howto » Entry Rules</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>
            <b>Aggregator</b> uses user-defined entry rules to filter out the entries
            of a feed.
          </p>
          <p>
            There are two types of rules: <b>exclude rules</b>, used to mark which
            entries should be hidden while aggregating a feed, and
            <b>include rules</b>, used to cancel the effect of some exclude rules.
          </p>
          <p>
            Every entry rule defines a <b>mask</b> used to match the entries for which
            the rule <b>action</b> is applied. The <i class="marked">%</i> character
            is used to match zero, one or multiple characters, and can be used
            multiple times in a <b>mask</b>.
          </p>
          <p>
            For example, the <i class="marked">%aggregator%</i> title mask will match
            every entry that contains <i class="marked">aggregator</i> in the title.
            While the <i class="marked">% Vol % Ch %</i> title mask will match every
            entry that contains both <i class="marked">&nbsp;Vol&nbsp;</i> and
            <i class="marked">&nbsp;Ch&nbsp;</i> (in the same order as present in the
             mask) in the title.
          </p>
          <h2>Excluding unwished entries</h2>
          <p>
            The easyest way to define rules that hide entries of a feed is by using
            the <b>exclude</b> action:
            <ol>
              <li>
                Select the entry which you want to exclude by <i>long pressing</i> it.
              </li>
              <li>
                Click the <i>exclude</i> action from the action bar.<br>
              </li>
            </ol>
          </p>
          <p>
            <i>
              NOTE: Depending on your device type, the <b>exclude</b> action can be
              found either as as an action icon or as an option in the overflow menu.
            </i>
          </p>
          <p>
            <i>
              HINT: Long pressing an icon in the action bar reveals the action name.
            </i>
          </p>
          <h2>Excluding all entries except the whished ones</h2>
          <p>
            This is achieved by defining at least two rules:
            <ol>
              <li>
                An <b>exclude</b> rule that hides every entry by using the following
                title mask: <i class="marked">%</i>
              </li>
              <li>
                One or more <b>include</b> rules that will cancel the effect of the
                <b>exclude</b> rule.
              </li>
            </ol>
          </p>
          <p>
            These rules are preferably created from the <i>entry rules</i> activity,
            which can be opened by clicking the <b>entry rules</b> option from the
            overflow menu.
          </p>
          <p>
            <i>
              NOTE: The <b>entry rules</b> activity lists all the rules of a feed,
              including the global ones, while also showing how many entries are
              matched by a rule.
            </i>
          </p>
        ]]>
      </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
